

# PEDRO GABRIEL CAIRES

Fullstack Developer

## PERSONAL SUMMARY

Hello world! My name is Pedro Gabriel and I'm a Fullstack Web and Mobile developer.

# **MY STORY**

I started programming when I was 14, I've always been a hardware and software lover, when I started to attend the Technician School in Computer Science it was a big definitive push into the area. In 2020, along with two long time friends, I created Phog Tech, a freelance team specialized in Web solutions. After that I participated in several Open Source projects and now I currently work at Simbiose Social, a social tech company. I stand out for my agility with new technologies and the ease of solving problems.

# **SKILLS**

- Javascript (React Native, Node.js & others)
  - PHP (Laravel, Codelgniter & others)
  - MySQL (& other relational databases)
    - Java
    - Kotlin
    - Flutter
    - Semantic HTML, CSS/SASS
      - Python
      - Docker
      - SOLID
    - AWS (& other cloud solutions)
      - Scrum/Kanban

#### **EDUCATION**

- "Curso Técnico em Informática" at Eniac College (2019~2021)
- College in Information Systems at FIAP (2022~Present)

# CONTACT

Cell Phone: +55 11 986341150 Email: pedrogcs0104@gmail.com

# LINKS

GITHUB: <a href="https://github.com/dgtyPedro">https://github.com/dgtyPedro</a>

**LinkedIn:** <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/pedrogabriel-caires/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/pedrogabriel-caires/</a>

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **PHOG TECH**

# PHP Back-End Developer (2020~2021)

I was responsible for structuring and developing all back-end of the projects that the team was hired.

## I'M LABS

#### Fullstack Developer (2021~2022)

An excellent opportunity in which on different projects I was exposed to several new and different technologies. I made several projects with ViteJs, NextJs, Laravel, Python, React Native and other technologies.

## SIMBIOSE SOCIAL

## Fullstack Developer (2022~Present)

The company I currently work for. I'm a "jack of all trades" type developer that creates features from the front-end to the back-end along with database structuring. I work extensively with Laravel, React.js, and MySQL.

## **NOTABLE PROJECTS**

- Simbiose's Platform: Platform that connects companies with NGOs made in ReactJs. LINK: <a href="https://simbiose.social">https://simbiose.social</a>
- Volumes & Markings: Measure application for liquid containers made 100% by me in React Native.

LINK:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.dooguitryx.volumesandmarkings

- dumpi-fy: Spotify playlist manager made 100% by me in PHP.

LINK: <a href="https://dumpi-fy.herokuapp.com">https://dumpi-fy.herokuapp.com</a>